# **ZULKIFUL MANSUR**

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Front end web developer recently qualified with a Diploma in Software Development from Code Institute. Presents ability to produce clean, maintainable and re-usable code. Possesses strong Problem Solving & Communication skills with experience in building responsive websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

### **WORK HISTORY**

Inbound, 08/2021 - Date Boohoo - Burnley, United Kingdom

• Processing of inbound items from suppliers

Brand Ambassador, 01/2022 – 03/2022 Cube Marketing - Manchester, United Kingdom

- Maintained up-to-date knowledge of industry trends, consumer behaviour and competitor activity to develop effective sales initiatives.
- Delivered professional sales presentations, creatively communicating product quality and market comparisons to prospective clients.

## Account Manager, Commercial Banking Division 02/2018 - 07/2021 Guaranty Trust Bank PLC - Abuja, Nigeria

- Effectively communicated with clients using well-developed interpersonal skills, helping to improve relationships and rapport.
- Built and strengthened relationships with new and existing accounts to drive revenue growth.

### **EDUCATION**

Front-End Web Development, 10/2021 – 10/2022 Code Institute via Learning People – United Kingdom

**Bachelor of Engineering, Mechanical Engineering, 07/2014 University of Sunderland** - Sunderland, SND

# **PROJECTS**

#### My Personal Website (Online CV)

Designed and built my landing page using HTML, CSS and Bootstrap as my first milestone project for Code Institute.

**GitHub link:** https://github.com/zeek-mansur/mysite/tree/master **Online Quiz Game** 

Designed and built an online quiz game using JavaScript, Jquery,HTML and CSS.

**Link:** https://zeek-mansur.github.io/Online\_Quiz/

### **CONTACT**

**Address:** 58 Buccleuch road Nelson, Lancashire BB9 7TE

**Phone:** 07749474228

Email: mzulkiful@yahoo.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/zulkifulmansur

**Website:** https://zeek-mansur.github.io/mysite/

### **CODING SKILLS**

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Git
- GitHub
- Bootsrap
- Jquery
- · React (Learning)
- Wireframes
- Responsive design & Mobile first websites

### SOFT SKILLS

- Communication & Interpersonal skill
- Strong problem-solving skill & critical thinking
- · Attention to detail
- Organizational skill
- Time management